#### Contact

ar6shahrzad@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/shahrzad-amirrahimi-1a4a82197 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

**JavaScript** 

HTML

Copywriting

### Languages

English (Elementary)

Persian (Native or Bilingual)

### Certifications

**SheCodes Basics** 

**SheCodes Basics** 

**SheCodes React** 

Quera college

SheCodes Responsive

# Shahrzad Amirrahimi

**Content Writer** 

Iran

### Summary

I have been working in the field of producing textual content and SEO since 2015.

I'm still working in the field of content creation and have my youtube channel which I create videos about things that I'm interested in, including anime and manga.

since 2019 I have started to learn Front-End. I'm very comfortable in HTML and CSS and designing the basic looks for websites. but JS is not my strong point. but I'm working on it and learning more about it. at the same time, I started to learn Python. I made few videos about it back in days but went back to learn Front-End again.

I'm working on my Japanese language and also learning German. I'm not fluent in English but the test I had before shows that I'm at an intermediate level.

part of my job as a content creator is to be able to read English texts and translate them to Persian. I also worked as a translator for Movies and dramas for 6 months

# Experience

Shahr mohtava
Content Writer
March 2020 - Present (3 years 8 months)

freelancer job Copy writer

Telewebion
Data Entry Operator
January 2020 - February 2022 (2 years 2 months)
Tehran, Iran

Filomo Translator

November 2020 - March 2021 (5 months)

Page 1 of 2

Tehran, Iran

emrc.info
Data Entry Operator
October 2019 - November 2019 (2 months)

Par30Game Content Writer August 2018 - September 2018 (2 months) Tehran, Iran

Brands Content Writer March 2018 - June 2018 (4 months)

Donamall
Content Writer
March 2018 - April 2018 (2 months)

Vandad informatic Copywriter December 2015 - March 2016 (4 months)

## Education

Bamdad Knowledge and Technology

Islamic Azad Univesity E-Campus
Bachelor's degree, Information Technology